uniquerewards.com 2008-12-21

# UniqueRewards: Get Paid to Take Online Surveys

User Log In

Testimonials

  * UR just changed my life! I've earned $400 for two days and bought my Palm Treo 700w!

Russel  
Fairfield, OH

  * This is the easiest way to earn some additional money for your needs!

Jessica  
Ann Arbor, MI

| 

UniqueRewards Privacy Statement

General: 

UniqueRewards strictly adheres to the Privacy Policy outlined below. We will closely guard any personally identifiable information you disclose to us during registration or at any other point during your UniqueRewards.com experience. 

Information will only be shared with a third party if a member requests that such information is to be shared. 

By joining UniqueRewards, you may choose to opt in or out of receiving our Newsletters. You can unsubscribe from UniqueRewards Mail at any time and still maintain an active UniqueRewards account. 

What Information UniqueRewards Collects: 

In order to receive any payment from the UniqueRewards service, we require all users to register via our online registration form. We require you to provide us with your full and correct name, full and correct street address, e-mail address and password. We will process this information to manage your membership, determine your eligibility, provide services, and allow you to take advantage of other member benefits. In addition to the information you provide to us in the online registration, we will also collect certain information online and offline arising out of your use of the UniqueRewards service, including but not limited to the number and type of offers you have responded to and completed. 

UniqueRewards.com will not share, sell, trade, or give away personally identifiable information to third parties without members' explicit permission. 

UniqueRewards.com collects online behavior statistical information regarding our members. Upon termination of the online session, closing of the browser and/or termination of your membership, this information will no longer be collected. Summaries of the information will be made available to third parties. Those summaries do not include members' names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or other personally identifiable information. 

Cookies: 

UniqueRewards uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on the UniqueRewards.com site and to save information on past activities and other preferences. 

Because of the cookie you don't have to reenter information upon every move throughout our site and you may complete offers without being prompted by our security system to log in again after each activity. When you log in to UniqueRewards.com, UniqueRewards reads the cookie to help target and personalize offers to you. UniqueRewards uses cookies for the benefit of users. UniqueRewards does not place any personally identifiable information in users' cookies. UniqueRewards does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. 

Data Security: 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, UniqueRewards has used appropriate and standard industry procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Such information includes the nature of your firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, UniqueRewards cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us or from our sponsors and you do so at your own risk. 

Links to Other Sites: 

The UniqueRewards web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that the company, UniqueRewards.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such linked sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. The UniqueRewards privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the UniqueRewards Web Site. 

Opting-Out: 

Established members will occasionally receive e-mails containing information regarding new offers or special promotions from UniqueRewards -- if they have not opted out. By "opting-out" the user indicates that he or she does not wish to receive such e-mails from UniqueRewards.com. The opt-out can be performed upon initial registration or later. You may optout of receiving these newsletters at any time by updating your account information in the UniqueRewards "My Profile" section. You can reach the "My Profile" section by clicking on the "My Profile" button in the main user's menu. When you reach this page, uncheck the box that reads, "Yes, I want to receive special cash offers". 

When a member receives a special offer or promotion e-mail from UniqueRewards.com and decides that he or she no longer wishes to receive such e-mails, the member can open the e-mail and scroll to the bottom. At the bottom of the e-mail page there will be a brief description of how to have an account "opted-out". Once UniqueRewards receives information regarding these account changes the company will make the specified changes as soon as possible. 

Site and Service Announcements: 

Under rare circumstances UniqueRewards.com may need to contact specific or all users in order to make an important announcement about the UniqueRewards site or service changes. Members are not able to unsubscribe, or "opt-out" of these announcements, because they may contain very important information regarding their accounts. Before these measures are taken, however, UniqueRewards will post information regarding changes directly on the web site. UniqueRewards.com reserves the right to contact users to correct account errors or to supply important information UniqueRewards deems relevant. 

Correction/Updating Personal Information: 

UniqueRewards users are able to change their personal information at any time. The fastest way to change personal information is to login to UniqueRewards.com and simply click on "My Profile". You will be prompted to enter your password again to change you personal information. If for some reason this page does not work, or there are any questions, users may contact our Member Support Team. Users should send our support team a clear and detailed e-mail message and our Member Support Team will see to it the proper changes are made to the user's account. 

SPAM 

We will immediately terminate any account, which we believe, at our sole discretion, is transmitting or is otherwise connected with any Spam or other unsolicited bulk e-mails and postings. 

We will not tolerate any such activities on our site or server of members who are involved in SPAM or related abuses. Our actions may include contacting relevant authorities (such as employers, universities, local law enforcement, the FBI) as well as asking Internet Service providers to deny service. 

SPAM includes, but is not limited to, unsolicited e-mails and/or postings in discussion groups, bulletin boards, and other public domain groups. Most network providers generally prohibit SPAM messages and in certain jurisdictions those users employing them may be subject to fines and/or imprisonment. We do not allow our members to utilize SPAM messages. The company will automatically terminate all spamming accounts. 

The only acceptable methods of referring someone to our UniqueRewards.com Rewards Online Program are through communication with family and friends, as well as through establishing a link to our web site on a member-owned Web site. 

To report spam, send an e-mail to: [abuse@UniqueRewards.com](mailto:abuse@UniqueRewards.com)

Canceling: 

You may cancel your Membership at anytime by clicking on the "Terminate Account" button on the "My Profile" section. If you do decide to cancel your membership, you can rejoin again at any time. 

Changes To The Privacy Policy: 

By registering to use the UniqueRewards service, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that UniqueRewards' s privacy policy is subject to change. We strongly advise our members to check back periodically to this page. We also welcome any feedback from you; please e-mail us at: [support@UniqueRewards.com](mailto:support@UniqueRewards.com) if you have any comments regarding the information provided or suggestions for improvements that can be made to this privacy policy. 

|  | 

**SearchCactus.com**

Earn Quick Cash! Fill out the first-page form and complete at least one offer on the next page.

Get $0.50

**Napster U.S.**

Napster - fast, safe and legal. Listen to full-length songs up to five times for FREE! Over 2 million songs with unlimited plays and CD quality sound for just $12.95 a month! 7-DAY FREE TRIAL! From now until Dec. 31, 2008 you can get a 1 GB Creative ZEN V MP3 player and 3 months of unlimited Napster To Go Music for only $49. A savings of 50%. That's right, a brand new MP3 player and 3 months of unlimited music for only $49!

Get $5.00

**SnagAJob.com**

Find a job that fits your schedule. Find part-time and full-time hourly positions on Snagajob.

Get $0.50

|
